A Guide to the Liberty Iron Furnace Collection, 1809-1917
Shenandoah County Library
A Guide to the Liberty Iron Furnace Collection, 1809-1917
Shenandoah County Library
29 boxes, 3 rolled storage boxes, 19 oversize folders.
The Liberty Iron Furnace Collection is comprised of 29 boxes of materials relating to three companies that operated the Liberty Iron Furnace during the late 19th and early 20th century. Approximately one half of the boxes contain correspondence and financial documents and the remaining boxes contain ledgers, day books, letter books, and other bound materials. The subject of the material is primarily business related and encompasses transactions, employment records, reports related to the railroad line, and other items.
Samuel G. Clark
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
This collection is open to researchers without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Placed on long term, permenant loan in memory of Samuel G. Clark of Liberty Furnace Virginia.
Biographical/Historical Information
In 1822 Walter Newman befan operating a furnace on a 900 acre piece of property he owned along Stony Creek, west of Edinburg Virginia. Newman called this site Liberty Furnace, a name that isretained today. Iron ore was mined and various furnaces were operated to refine that ore between that year and the early part of the 20th century.
Scope and Content
The Liberty Iron Furnace Collection consists of approximately 34.5 linear feet of material. This includes 224 folders of documents, 74 folders of documents previously stored in ledger books, a collection of technical drawings, maps and plat drawings, surveys, and approximately 51 ledgers, checkbooks, day books, and other bound items. They are stored in 29 boxes, 8 rolled storage boxes, and 19 oversize folders. The collection is organized into the following seven series
Series 1, Letter Box March 31 1918 includes of correspondence found in a letter box labeled March 31, 1918. The correspondence covers the 1909-1910 period and is sorted alphabetically as found in the letter box.
Series 2, Letter Box, Receiver L.S. Company, 1891-1892 includes correspondence found in a letter box Labeled Receiver L.S. Company, 1891. The documents covers the 1909-1912 time period and is sorted as found in the letter box.
Series 3, Receivership Documents, July 1891-February 1892 includes receipts and documents related to the time period when the Liberty Iron Company was placed in receivership. It is sorted chronologically as originally found.
Series 4, Dedford Company Correspondence, 1901-1909 includes items related to the Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company's transactions with the Dedford Company of Luray Virginia which purchased lumber and bark for its tannery operation.
Series 5, Bark Reports and Receipts, 1905-1911 includes reports and receipts for bark shipped by the Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company to various businesses during that period. These are sorted chronologically and were found together.
Series 6, Correspondence, 1909-1917 includes a wide array of records, correspondence, and other documents related to the operations of the Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company and its successor from 1909-1917. These are sorted chronologically and were found stored together.
Series 7, Ledgers, 1874-1913 includes a wide array of bound record books including ledgers, employment logs, day books, account books, checkbooks, receipt books, and other journals. It covers the operation of the Wissler furnaces, the Liberty Iron Company, and Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company and is stored as size permits.
Series 8, Maps and Plats, 1891-1899 includes maps of the company's rail line, surveys of company land holdings, and maps related to the company's operation. The bulk appear to have been created sometime around 1900, but the bulk of the items are undated.
Series 9, Technical Drawings, undated includes a single folder with technical drawings related to the company's machinery. While most of the items have identifying labels, they are undated.
Series 10, Payroll Records, 1905-1910 includes payroll sheets retained by the company between 1905 and 1910. They list employees and the amount they were paid by month. They are sorted chronologically and were found stored together.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in ten (10) series.
Contents List
- Series I: Letter Box March 31 1918 (Box 1)
  - Series Information Sheet, May 9 2017 (Folder 1.1)
  - Correspondence A, 1909-1910 (Folder 1.2)
  - Correspondence B, 1909-1910 (Folder 1.3)
  - Correspondence C, 1909-1910 (Folder 1.4)
  - Correspondence D, 1909-1910 (Folder 1.5)
  - Correspondence E, 1909-1910 (Folder 1.6)
  - Correspondence F, 1909 (Folder 1.7)
  - Correspondence G, 1909-1910 (Folder 1.8)
  - Correspondence I/J, 1905-1910 (Folder 1.9)
  - Correspondence K/L, 1908-1910 (Folder 1.10)
  - Correspondence M/N/O, 1909 (Folder 1.11)
  - Correspondence P/Q, 1909 (Folder 1.12)
  - Correspondence R, 1909-1910 (Folder 1.13)
  - Correspondence S, 1909-1910, 1 of 3 (Folder 1.14)
  - Correspondence S, 1909-1910, 2 of 3 (Folder 1.15)
  - Correspondence S, 1909-1910, 3 of 3 (Folder 1.16)
  - Correspondence, Shenandoah National Bank Cards, 1909 (Folder 1.17)
  - Correspondence T-Z, 1908-1910, 1 of 2 (Folder 1.18)
  - Correspondence T-Z, 1908-1910,2 of 2 (Folder 1.19)
- Series II: Letter Box, Receiver L.S. Company, 1891-1892 (Box 2)
  - Series Information Sheet, May 8 2017 (Folder 2.1)
  - The Dedford Company, Luray Virginia, 1909 (Folder 2.2)
  - Stokesville Bark, Stokesville Virginia, May-December 1909 (Folder 2.3)
  - J.P. Houck Tanning Company, Harrisonburg Virginia January-December 1909 (Folder 2.4)
  - Statement of Engineer (Railroad), 1911-1912 (Folder 2.5)
  - Insurance Correspondence, 1909-1910 (Folder 2.6)
  - Henkel and McCauley Timber, Moorefield West Virginia, 1910 (Folder 2.7)
  - Registry Return Receipts, 1909 (Folder 2.8)
  - Correspondence, 1909-1910 (Folder 2.9)
  - Financial Notes, Receipts, and Accounts, 1909-1911 (Folder 2.10)
- Series III: Receivership Documents, July 1891-February 1892 (Box 3)
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company Receipts, July-August 1891 (Folder 3.1)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, August 1891 (Folder 3.2)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, September 1891 1 of 2 (Folder 3.3)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, September 1891 2 of 2 (Folder 3.4)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, October 1891 1 of 2 (Folder 3.5)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, October 1891 2 of 2 (Folder 3.6)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, November 1891 1 of 2 (Folder 3.7)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, November 1891 2 of 2 (Folder 3.8)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, December 1891 1 of 2 (Folder 3.9)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, December 1891 2 of 2 (Folder 3.10)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, January 1892 1 of 3 (Folder 3.11)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, January 1892 2 of 3 (Folder 3.12)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, January 1892 3 of 3 (Folder 3.13)
  - Liberty Iron Company Receivership Documents, February 1892 (Folder 3.14)
- Series IV: Dedford Company Correspondence, 1904-1909 (Box 4)
  - Dedford Company Contract, May 6, 1905 (Folder 4.1)
  - Dedford Company Bark Weights Envelope, June 1907 (Folder 4.2)
  - Bills of Lading for Bark for Dedford Company, July 1907 (Folder 4.3)
  - Report for Dedford, July 1907 (Folder 4.4)
  - Bark Shipments for Dedford Company, July 1907 (Folder 4.5)
  - Dedford Bark Shipment Envelope, July 1907 (Folder 4.6)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts Envelope, September 1907 (Folder 4.7)
  - Dedford and Company Bark Receipts, October 1907 (Folder 4.8)
  - Dedford and Company Bark Receipts, November 1907 (Folder 4.9)
- Series IV: Dedford Company Correspondence, 1904-1909 (Box 5)
  - Bills of Lading, Bark for Dedford Company, December 1907 (Folder 5.1)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, May 1908 (Folder 5.2)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts and Shipments, June 1908 (Folder 5.3)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts and Shipments, June-July 1908 (Folder 5.4)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, June 1908 (Folder 5.5)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, July 1908 (Folder 5.6)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts and Shipments, July -August 1908 (Folder 5.7)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, August 1908 (Folder 5.8)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts and Shipments, August-September 1908 (Folder 5.9)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, September 1908 (Folder 5.10)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts and Railroad Shipments, September-October 1908 (Folder 5.11)
  - "Stubs", Dedford Company Bark Receipts, September-October 1908 (Folder 5.12)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts and Shipments, October-December 1908 (Folder 5.13)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, October 1908 (Folder 5.14)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, Cornelius Miller and Oliver Vann, Nov 1908 (Folder 5.15)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, November 1908 (Folder 5.16)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, J.M. Barton, November-December 1908 (Folder 5.17)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts and Railway Shipments, Dec 1908-Jan 1909 (Folder 5.18)
  - Dedford Company Account Sheets, 1908 (Folder 5.19)
  - "Bark Receipts-Voucher etc. for 1908", Dedford Company Bark Receipt Wrapping (Folder 5.20)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, 1908, omitted from 1907 Settlement (Folder 5.21)
  - Wagon Reports, Dedford and Company, August Bark 1909 (Folder 5.22)
- Series III: Receivership Documents, July 1891-February 1892 (Box 26)
  - Dedford Company Bark Shipments, July 1907 (1 of 3)
  - Dedford Company Bark Shipments, July 1907 (2 of 3)
  - Dedford Company Bark Shipments, July 1907 (3 of 3)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, August 1907 (1 of 2)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, August 1907 (2 of 2)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, September 1907 (1 of 3)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, September 1907 (2 of 3)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, September 1907 (3 of 3)
  - Dedford Company Bark Weights June 1907 (1 of 2)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts June 1907 (2 of 2)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, October 1907 (1 of 3)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, October 1907 (2 of 3)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, October 1907 (3 of 3))
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, November 1907 (1 of 3)
  - Dedford Company Bank Receipts, November 1907, (2 of 3)
  - Dedford Company Bark Receipts, November 1907, (3 of 3)
- Series V: Bark Reports and Receipts 1905-1911 (Box 6)
  - Bark Contracts, 1905-1906 (Folder 6.1)
  - Lumber and Bark Contracts, 1906-1907 1 of 3 (Folder 6.2)
  - Lumber and Bark Contracts, 1906-1907 2 of 3 (Folder 6.3)
  - Lumber and Bark Contracts, 1906-1907 3 of 3 (Folder 6.4)
  - Bark Shipments, August 1907 (Folder 6.5)
  - Bark Reports, January 1911 (Folder 6.6)
  - Bark Shipments, September 1907 (Folder 6.7)
  - Contracts for Bark, 1908 (Folder 6.8)
  - Bark Records, 1908 (Folder 6.9)
  - Orders on Payment for Bark, J. Bradfield, 1908 (Folder 6.10)
  - Bark Receipts, Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company, May-July 1909 (Folder 6.11)
  - J.P. Hauck Bark, November 1909 (Folder 6.12)
  - Bark Contracts, 1909 (Folder 6.13)
  - Bark Receipts, 1909 (Folder 6.14)
  - Bark Delivery Receipts, 1909 (Folder 6.15)
  - Bark with Charles L. Ryman of St. Luke, April 16 1910 (Folder 6.16)
  - Bark Shipments, May and June Reports, 1910 (Folder 6.17)
  - Bark Reports, July 1910 (Folder 6.18)
  - Contracts, 1910 (Folder 6.19)
  - September Bark, 1910 (Folder 6.20)
  - October Bark Reports, 1910 (Folder 6.21)
  - Bark Reports, November 1910 (Folder 6.22)
  - Moses Markle Bark Receipts, 1910 (Folder 6.23)
  - Bark Tickets, August 1910 (Folder 6.24)
  - Reports of Wagon Bark Received, 1910 (Folder 6.25)
  - Bark Delivery Receipts, August-September 1911 (Folder 6.26)
  - August Bark, 1910 (Folder 6.27)
  - Bark Tickets, 1911 (Folder 6.28)
- Series VI: Documents, 1809-1917 (Box 7)
  - Deer Head Tract, Memoranda of Adjacent Title, map, etc., 1809-1891 (Folder 7.1)
  - Land Purchases, Jacob Wisler, 1867-1891 (Folder 7.2)
  - Land Deeds and Surveys, 1870-1910 (Folder 7.3)
  - Land Deeds and Surveys, 1871-1904 (Folder 7.4)
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company Receipts, 1891 (Folder 7.5)
  - Report of M.M. Campbell Receiver of Liberty Iron Company, Receipts and Expenditures, June 24 1891-August 1, 1892 (Folder 7.6)
  - 7 Georgia Home Insurance Company Policy, 1892 (Folder 7.7)
  - Commissary Department Order Book, February-March 1905 (Folder 7.8)
  - Letter from George Conrad Attorney to W.D. Brelsford Concerning Trust, March 10 1905 (Folder 7.9)
  - Receipts for Trust Deeds, American Security and Trust Company, May 1905 (Folder 7.10)
  - Deed of Trust Payment, October 1905 (Folder 7.11)
  - Orkney Spring 1405 Acre Tract, 1905 (Folder 7.12)
  - Cyrus Borgner Company Correspondence, 1905 (Folder 7.13)
  - Railway Mail Service, 1905-1906 (Folder 7.14)
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Check Stub Book, 1905-1906 (Folder 7.15)
  - Report of Sales of Land Made by Judge E.D. Newman, August 11 1905 to June 18 1908 (Folder 7.16)
  - Railway Mail Service Correspondence, 1905-1909 (Folder 7.17)
  - Statements of Accounts, Assets, and Expenditures, 1905-1909 (Folder 7.18)
  - Riggs National Bank, Washinton DC, Correspondence, 1905-1910 (Folder 7.19)
- Series VI: Documents, 1809-1917 (Box 8)
  - Letters P.M. (postmaster) General, May 1906 (Folder 8.1)
  - Receipt for E.W. Newman for note, July 1906 (Folder 8.2)
  - Time Book, 1906 (Folder 8.3)
  - Maps of Land Tracts, ca. 1906 (Folder 8.4)
  - Land and Note Documents, 1906 (Folder 8.5)
  - Report on James McKelvey, Sommerset Pennsylvania, 1906 (Folder 8.6)
  - "Tax Receipts for 1896", 1906-1908 (Folder 8.7)
  - Petty Cash Receipts, January 1907 (Folder 8.8)
  - Petty Cash Receipts, February - March 1907 (Folder 8.9)
  - Receipts for Petty Cash, March 1907 (Folder 8.10)
  - Petty Cash Receipts for April 1907 (Folder 8.11)
  - Timber Contract between Iron and Coal Company and Eliga Pilton, May 1907 (Folder 8.12)
  - Lease with Robert Sherman, June 1, 1907 (Folder 8.13)
  - Water Contract, Town of Edinburg, June 25, 1907 (Folder 8.14)
  - Petty Cash Receipts, June 1907 (Folder 8.15)
  - Lease between Shenandoah Iron and Coal and W.L. Clark of Edinburg Virginia, September 1, 1907 (Folder 8.16)
  - Petty Cash Paid, September 1907 (Folder 8.17)
  - Southern Railway Agreement, October 9, 1907 (Folder 8.18)
  - Report on Charcoal Available on Orkney Springs Tract, R.L. Sherman to W.L. Merriam, October 11, 1907 (Folder 8.19)
  - Petty Cash Vouchers October 1907 (Folder 8.20)
  - Receipts for Petty Cash, October-December 1907 (Folder 8.21)
  - Freight Bills and Express, October-December 1907 (Folder 8.22)
  - Petty Cash Receipts 1907 (Folder 8.23)
  - S.J. & C. Company Bark Receipts, 1907 (Folder 8.24)
  - Jacob Johnson Bark Weights, 1907 (Folder 8.25)
  - Tool List, 1907 (Folder 8.26)
  - Financial Correspondence and Documents, 1907-1912 (Folder 8.27)
  - Stockholders Meeting, June 1908 (Folder 8.28)
  - Letter to W.R. Merriam from Samuel Maddox concerning trip, November 23, 1908 (Folder 8.29)
  - Store Inventory, December 1908 (Folder 8.30)
  - J.R. Ryman, Milton Miller, and Kingrey-Vann Contracts, 1908 (Folder 8.31)
- Series VI: Documents, 1809-1917 (Box 9)
  - Shorthand Notebook, ca. 1909 (Folder 9.1)
  - Contracts for 1909 (Folder 9.2)
  - Smooth and Day, Bark Contracts, 1909 (Folder 9.3)
  - Correspondence and Financial Documents, 1909-1914 (Folder 9.4)
  - Trees and Lumber Receipts, January-May 1910 (Folder 9.5)
  - Jack Riffee Contract, August 1910 (Folder 9.6)
  - Logging Agreement, August 15, 1910 (Folder 9.7)
  - Foltz B.S., Chemical, 1910 (Folder 9.8)
  - Lantz and Lindamood Lumber Company, 1910-1914 (Folder 9.9)
  - Letter from W.A. Wrenn Produce Dealer concerning payment, August 19, 1911 (Folder 9.10)
  - I.P. Wittig Company, 1911 (Folder 9.11)
  - ________ Statements, Monroe Miller, 1911 (Folder 9.12)
  - Financial Documents, 1912 (Folder 9.13)
  - Unidentified Correspondence, 1912 (Folder 9.14)
  - Paid Checks, July 1913 (Folder 9.15)
  - Check Stubs, July-August 1913 (Folder 9.16)
  - Thomas Foltz, August 1913 (Folder 9.17)
  - Paid Checks, September 1913 (Folder 9.18)
  - ________ Thomas Foltz Government Receipts, 1913 (Folder 9.19)
  - Paid Checks, July-October 1914 (Folder 9.20)
  - Deed Information sent to Tom Foltz, Liberty Furnace Virginia, August 20, 1914 (Folder 9.21)
  - Letter to "Thomas Foltz, Esq", from W.R. Merriam concerning Miller Suit, September 18, 1914 (Folder 9.22)
  - Shorthand Notebook, ca. 1914 (Folder 9.23)
  - Rife Hydraulic Engine Manufacturing Company, 1914 (Folder 9.24)
  - George Williams, agreement for house rent, 1914 (Folder 9.25)
  - Hauck Tannery Receipts, 1914 (Folder 9.26)
- Series VI: Documents, 1809-1917 (Box 10)
  - Columbia Roller Mills Invoices, Paid, 1914 (Folder 10.1)
  - Check Subs, February 1914-January 1915 (Folder 10.2)
  - Paid Checks, January 1915 (Folder 10.3)
  - Checks Drawn, January-September 1915 (Folder 10.4)
  - Paid Checks, March 1915 (Folder 10.5)
  - Paid Checks, May 1915-May 1916 (Folder 10.6)
  - Columbia Roller Mills Receipts, 1915 (Folder 10.7)
  - Assorted Financial Notes and Figures, 1915-1916 (Folder 10.8)
  - Farmer's Bank of Edinburg Deposits and Credits, 1915-1916 (Folder 10.9)
  - Paid Checks, May-June, 1916 (Folder 10.10)
  - Letter from Joseph T. Jackson to Thomas Foltz concerning chicken broilers and repairs, July 30, 1916 (Folder 10.11)
  - Paid Checks, 1916 (Folder 10.12)
  - Paid Checks, January-November 1917 (Folder 10.13)
  - Columbia Roller Mills Receipts, 1917 (Folder 10.14)
  - Undated Survey Copy (Folder 10.15)
  - Financial Account Notes, undated (Folder 10.16)
  - "Volume Number 33, Illustrations of Modern Blast Furnaces, William Pollock Company" and Local Drawings, undated (Folder 10.17)
  - The Shenandoah County Bank Checkbook, undated (Folder 10.18)
  - Personnel Account Sheets, undated (Folder 10.19)
  - Triplet and Irving Freight Hauling Invoices, undated (Folder 10.20)
  - Threat to Destroy "Dinky" Railroad, undated (Folder 10.21)
  - Newland Tract Survey with Notes, undated (Folder 10.22)
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company By-Laws, undated (Folder 10.23)
  - Wagon Bark Receipts, July 1910 (Folder 10.24)
  - Monarch Blast Furnace Company Ledger Pages, 1905 (Folder 10.25)
  - Wagon Bark Received Receipts, July 1914 (Folder 10.26)
- Series VI: Documents, 1809-1917, North Mountain Iron Company First Mortgage Loan 1906 (Folder OVERSIZE FOLDER 3)
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 11)
  - Document found page 57 "S.E." Ledger, 1890 (Folder 11.1)
  - Page found Index Page "T" Cash and Inventory Book, 1890-1904 (Folder 11.2)
  - Document found page 133, Cash and Inventory Book, 1890-1904 (Folder 11.3)
  - Documents found page 1, Liberty Iron Company Ledger, 1891 (Folder 11.4)
  - Document found page 184-185, Day Book February - December 1892 (Folder 11.5)
  - Document found "August 13, 1892" page, Liberty Iron Company, Liberty Reports #9, May 1892-January 1893 (Folder 11.6)
  - Pages found front of Account Book, August 1892 (Folder 11.7)
  - Documents found inside Front Cover, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.8)
  - Documents found inside Jacket page C/D, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.9)
  - Documents found inside page 81, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.10)
  - Documents found inside page 91, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.11)
  - Documents found inside page 93, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.12)
  - Documents found inside page 97, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.13)
  - Documents found inside page 99, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.14)
  - Documents found inside page 101, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.15)
  - Documents found inside page 103, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.16)
  - Documents found inside page 111, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.17)
  - Documents found inside page 112-113, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.18)
  - Documents found inside page 118-119, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.19)
  - Documents found inside page 123, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.20)
  - Documents found inside page 125, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.21)
  - Documents found inside page 126-127, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.22)
  - Documents found inside page 130-131, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.23)
  - Documents found inside page 150-151, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.24)
  - Documents found inside page 154-155, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.25)
  - Documents found inside page 156-157, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.26)
  - Documents found inside page 164-165, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.27)
  - Documents found inside page 168-169, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.28)
  - Documents found inside page 174-175, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.29)
  - Documents found inside page 182-183, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.30)
  - Documents found inside page 202-203, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.31)
  - Documents found inside page 206-207, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.32)
  - Documents found inside page 214-215, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.33)
  - Documents found inside page 222-223, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.34)
  - Documents found inside page 224-225, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.35)
  - Documents found inside page 226-227, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.36)
  - Documents found inside page 228-229, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.37)
  - Documents found inside page 240-241, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.38)
  - Documents found inside page 244-245, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.39)
  - Documents found inside page 248-249, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.40)
  - Documents found inside page 254-255, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.41)
  - Documents found inside page 268-269, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.42)
  - Documents found inside page 270-271, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.43)
  - Documents found inside page 274-275, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.44)
  - Documents found inside page 276-277, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.45)
  - Documents found inside page 280-281, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.46)
  - Documents found inside page 286-287, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.47)
  - Documents found inside page 298-299, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.48)
  - Documents found inside page 302-303, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.49)
  - Documents found inside page 324-325, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.50)
  - Documents found inside page 328-329, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.51)
  - Documents found inside page 323-333, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.52)
  - Documents found inside page 350-351, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.53)